<!DOCTYPE html>
<html lang="en">
<head>
<meta charset="UTF-8">
<title>Privacy Policy</title>
<meta name="title" content="Privacy Policy">
<meta name="DC.title" lang="en" content="Privacy Policy">
<meta name="description" content="<p>Discover how to streamline your Amazon FBA accounting effortlessly with Link My Books. Save time and improve accuracy in just a few clicks!</p><p>Streamline your online business with top ecommerce bookkeeping solutions. Accurate, efficient, and tailored for e-commerce success.</p><p>Streamline your ecommerce with real-time bookkeeping. Fast, accurate financial insights to drive business growth.</p><p>Streamline your online store with automated bookkeeping. Efficient, accurate, and time-saving financial management.</p><p>"Streamline your business with efficient inventory management and precise bookkeeping for optimal operational success."</p><p>Optimize your ecommerce success with efficient sales tracking tools. Monitor, analyze, and improve your sales strategies effectively.</p><p>"Streamline your ecommerce finances with tax-ready bookkeeping solutions designed for simplicity and compliance."</p><p>Master your finances with efficient tracking of income and expenses. Gain control and improve your financial health effortlessly!</p><p>Master multi-channel sales bookkeeping: streamline tracking, optimize revenue, and enhance financial accuracy across platforms.</p><p>Seamlessly integrate your ecommerce platform with accounting software to streamline finances and improve accuracy.</p><p>Streamline your ecommerce finances with our cloud-based bookkeeping solutions. Secure, scalable, and accessible anywhere.</p><p>Explore methods to evaluate and enhance the profitability of your products efficiently. Boost your financial success!</p><p>Streamline your business with efficient order management and precise bookkeeping for improved accuracy and profitability.</p><p>Discover efficient ecommerce bookkeeping with automation. Streamline finances and save time for strategic business growth.</p><p>"Ecommerce Revenue Tracking: Essential tools and strategies to monitor and boost your online sales efficiently."</p><p>Efficiently manage your financial transactions by reconciling payments and payouts to ensure accuracy and maintain fiscal health.</p><p>Master Shopify ecommerce bookkeeping with tailored strategies to streamline finances and boost profitability.</p><p>Efficiently manage and reconcile transactions in multiple currencies with our precise multi-currency bookkeeping solutions.</p><p>Ensure your ecommerce business meets all sales tax compliance requirements to avoid penalties and optimize operations.</p><p>Efficiently track and manage stock levels with our product inventory bookkeeping tools—optimize costs and enhance operational effectiveness.</p><p>Discover top ecommerce financial reporting tools to track sales, expenses, and profits efficiently, enhancing your business decisions.</p><p>Discover how to optimize your online store's cash flow with effective tracking tools and strategies. Boost profitability and growth.</p><p>Optimize your e-commerce financials with precise expense categorization, boosting efficiency and profitability.</p><p>Learn essential bookkeeping strategies for ecommerce marketplaces to optimize financial management and boost profitability.</p><p>Explore key principles and strategies for accurately recognizing revenue from online sales, ensuring compliance and financial accuracy.</p><p>Efficient bookkeeping software tailored for Amazon sellers to simplify finances, track sales, and optimize business operations.</p><p>Streamline your e-commerce business with efficient payroll and expense tracking solutions, enhancing accuracy and financial health.</p><p>Streamline your ecommerce with automated invoicing. Save time, reduce errors, and enhance customer satisfaction.</p><p>Track profit margins by product to optimize pricing, streamline operations, and boost profitability efficiently.</p><p>Streamline your ecommerce with effective order reconciliation to ensure accuracy in inventory, payments, and customer satisfaction.</p><p>Streamline your ecommerce finances with expert bank reconciliation services, ensuring accuracy and efficiency in your financial management.</p><p>Simplify your online business with efficient eCommerce tax filing integration, ensuring accuracy and compliance effortlessly.</p><p>Streamline your ecommerce finances with our expert monthly bookkeeping services—accurate, timely, and tailored for online businesses.</p><p>Streamline and optimize your sales with multi-channel ecommerce accounting for accurate, real-time financial insights across platforms.</p><p>Monitor your online store's earnings instantly with real-time ecommerce profit tracking. Boost efficiency and profitability effortlessly!</p><p>Explore efficient bookkeeping strategies tailored for digital products to optimize financial management and compliance.</p><p>Streamline your ecommerce operations with efficient accounts payable management. Optimize cash flow and vendor relations effortlessly!</p><p>Efficiently integrate your sales channels with bookkeeping for streamlined financial management and real-time insights.</p><p>Learn key strategies for effective inventory valuation to boost your ecommerce business's efficiency and profitability.</p><p>Discover essential bookkeeping tips for ecommerce businesses to streamline finances and boost profitability.</p><p>Efficiently monitor and manage recurring expenses to optimize budgeting and financial planning.</p><p>Optimize your ecommerce success with effective vendor management strategies to streamline operations and boost profitability.</p><p>Master product returns bookkeeping: streamline refunds, manage inventory, and optimize financial records efficiently.</p><p>Automate your finance management with precise transaction categorization for efficient tracking and reporting.</p><p>Discover top eCommerce expense tracking tools to streamline your finances, increase efficiency, and boost profits. Perfect for online businesses!</p><p>Learn essential methods for calculating Cost of Goods Sold (COGS) in e-commerce to optimize your inventory and pricing strategies.</p><p>Discover key strategies for effective eCommerce financial forecasting. Optimize profits with accurate sales, budget, and trend analysis.</p><p>Seamlessly integrate top payment gateways to enhance your ecommerce platform's checkout process and boost sales.</p><p>Master ecommerce bookkeeping with advanced reporting techniques to optimize profits and streamline financial management.</p><p>Explore essential bookkeeping tips for ecommerce subscription services to streamline finances and boost profitability.</p>">
<meta name="robots" content="index, follow">
<meta name="googlebot" content="index, follow, max-snippet:-1, max-image-preview:large, max-video-preview:-1">
<meta name="bingbot" content="index, follow, max-snippet:-1, max-image-preview:large, max-video-preview:-1">
<link rel="canonical" href="privacy-policy.html">
<link rel="shortcut icon"  href="img/logo.jpg"/>
<link rel="stylesheet" href="https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/npm/bootstrap@4.6.1/dist/css/bootstrap.min.css">
<link rel="stylesheet" href="https://fonts.googleapis.com/css?family=Kumbh+Sans:100,200,300,400,500,600,700,800,900&amp;display=swap" as="style" onload="this.onload=null;this.rel='stylesheet'">
<script src="https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/npm/jquery@3.5.1/dist/jquery.slim.min.js"></script>
<script src="https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/npm/popper.js@1.16.1/dist/umd/popper.min.js"></script>
<script src="https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/npm/bootstrap@4.6.1/dist/js/bootstrap.bundle.min.js"></script>
<link rel="stylesheet" href="https://cdnjs.cloudflare.com/ajax/libs/font-awesome/4.7.0/css/font-awesome.min.css">
<style type="text/css">
.fb4711af5072b2e4691d35da813eac0c8:hover{
box-shadow: 0 49.6px 50.5px -25px rgb(0 0 0 / 30%);
transform: rotate(-2deg) scale(1.03);
}
.btn-md{
padding: 15.2px 30px;
border-radius: 0;
}
a{
text-decoration: none!important;
}
a:hover{
color:#ffffff;background:#ffc658!important;
}
.y8ca88ea9680eb3ce14683d78ff3a39c6 a{
font-size:16px;
}
footer *{
font-size:16px !important;
}
ul{
list-style: circle;
}
html{
scroll-behavior: smooth;
}
.bea14ca84507e18b21dddfb9118578681{
background-color:#ffc107!important;
border-color:#ffc107!important;
color:#000000!important;
}
*{
font-family: 'Kumbh Sans', sans-serif;
}
.y8ca88ea9680eb3ce14683d78ff3a39c6 p,.y8ca88ea9680eb3ce14683d78ff3a39c6 span,.y8ca88ea9680eb3ce14683d78ff3a39c6 label{
font-size:16px!important;
}
.nav-link{
color: #000000;

}
.navbar a{
font-size: 18.3px!important;
font-weight: bold;
}
.cc94b12ad53c37ae39926399873739162 p,.cc94b12ad53c37ae39926399873739162 a,.cc94b12ad53c37ae39926399873739162 span,.cc94b12ad53c37ae39926399873739162 label{
font-size:16px!important;
}
.cc94b12ad53c37ae39926399873739162 a,.y8ca88ea9680eb3ce14683d78ff3a39c6 a{
color:#141414!important;
text-decoration: underline !important;
}
footer a{
color:#ffffff;
text-decoration: underline;
}
.nav-item{
padding-left:8.3px;
padding-right:8.1px;
padding-top:5.1px;
padding-bottom:5.3px;
}
footer{
background:#070707;
color:#ffffff;
}
</style>
</head>
<body>
<nav class="navbar-expand-lg navbar">
<a class="navbar-brand" href="index.html"  ><img alt="img/logo.jpg" src="img/logo.jpg" ></a>
<button class="navbar-toggler" type="button" data-toggle="collapse" data-target="#navbarSupportedContent" aria-controls="navbarSupportedContent" aria-expanded="false" aria-label="Toggle navigation">
<span class="navbar-toggler-icon"></span></button><div class="navbar-collapse collapse" id="navbarSupportedContent">
<ul class="align-items-center d-flex ml-auto navbar-nav"><li class="nav-item">
<a class="nav-link bccd5f007a9ef819a33b706381fe41441" href="index.html" >How to automate Amazon FBA accounting with Link My Books</a>
</li>
<li class="nav-item">
<a class="bccd5f007a9ef819a33b706381fe41441 nav-link" href="ecommerce-bookkeeping-solutions.html" >Ecommerce Bookkeeping Solutions</a>
</li>
<li class="nav-item">
<a class="bccd5f007a9ef819a33b706381fe41441 nav-link" href="real-time-bookkeeping-for-ecommerce.html" >Real-Time Bookkeeping for Ecommerce</a>
</li>
<li class="nav-item">
<a class="nav-link bccd5f007a9ef819a33b706381fe41441" href="automated-bookkeeping-for-online-stores.html" >Automated Bookkeeping for Online Stores</a>
</li>
<li class="nav-item dropdown">
<a class="bccd5f007a9ef819a33b706381fe41441 nav-link dropdown-toggle" href="#" id="navbarDropdown" role="button" data-toggle="dropdown" aria-expanded="false">More</a>
<div class="dropdown-menu-right dropdown-menu" aria-labelledby="navbarDropdown">
<a class="dropdown-item" href="inventory-management-and-bookkeeping.html"  >Inventory Management and Bookkeeping</a><a class="dropdown-item" href="sales-tracking-for-ecommerce-businesses.html"  >Sales Tracking for Ecommerce Businesses</a><a class="dropdown-item" href="tax-ready-ecommerce-bookkeeping.html"  >Tax-Ready Ecommerce Bookkeeping</a><a class="dropdown-item" href="income-and-expense-tracking.html"  >Income and Expense Tracking</a><a class="dropdown-item" href="multi-channel-sales-bookkeeping.html"  >Multi-Channel Sales Bookkeeping</a><a class="dropdown-item" href="ecommerce-accounting-integrations.html"  >Ecommerce Accounting Integrations</a><a class="dropdown-item" href="cloud-based-bookkeeping-for-ecommerce.html"  >Cloud-Based Bookkeeping for Ecommerce</a><a class="dropdown-item" href="product-profitability-analysis.html"  >Product Profitability Analysis</a><a class="dropdown-item" href="order-management-bookkeeping.html"  >Order Management & Bookkeeping</a><a class="dropdown-item" href="ecommerce-bookkeeping-with-automation.html"  >Ecommerce Bookkeeping with Automation</a><a class="dropdown-item" href="ecommerce-revenue-tracking.html"  >Ecommerce Revenue Tracking</a><a class="dropdown-item" href="reconcile-payments-and-payouts.html"  >Reconcile Payments and Payouts</a><a class="dropdown-item" href="ecommerce-bookkeeping-for-shopify.html"  >Ecommerce Bookkeeping for Shopify</a><a class="dropdown-item" href="multi-currency-bookkeeping.html"  >Multi-Currency Bookkeeping</a><a class="dropdown-item" href="sales-tax-compliance-for-ecommerce.html"  >Sales Tax Compliance for Ecommerce</a><a class="dropdown-item" href="product-inventory-bookkeeping.html"  >Product Inventory Bookkeeping</a><a class="dropdown-item" href="ecommerce-financial-reporting-tools.html"  >Ecommerce Financial Reporting Tools</a><a class="dropdown-item" href="cash-flow-tracking-for-online-retailers.html"  >Cash Flow Tracking for Online Retailers</a><a class="dropdown-item" href="ecommerce-expense-categorization.html"  >Ecommerce Expense Categorization</a><a class="dropdown-item" href="bookkeeping-for-ecommerce-marketplaces.html"  >Bookkeeping for Ecommerce Marketplaces</a><a class="dropdown-item" href="revenue-recognition-for-online-sales.html"  >Revenue Recognition for Online Sales</a><a class="dropdown-item" href="bookkeeping-software-for-amazon-sellers.html"  >Bookkeeping Software for Amazon Sellers</a><a class="dropdown-item" href="ecommerce-payroll-and-expense-tracking.html"  >Ecommerce Payroll and Expense Tracking</a><a class="dropdown-item" href="automated-invoicing-for-ecommerce.html"  >Automated Invoicing for Ecommerce</a><a class="dropdown-item" href="profit-margin-tracking-by-product.html"  >Profit Margin Tracking by Product</a><a class="dropdown-item" href="ecommerce-order-reconciliation.html"  >Ecommerce Order Reconciliation</a><a class="dropdown-item" href="bank-reconciliation-for-ecommerce.html"  >Bank Reconciliation for Ecommerce</a><a class="dropdown-item" href="ecommerce-tax-filing-integration.html"  >Ecommerce Tax Filing Integration</a><a class="dropdown-item" href="monthly-bookkeeping-for-ecommerce.html"  >Monthly Bookkeeping for Ecommerce</a><a class="dropdown-item" href="multi-channel-ecommerce-accounting.html"  >Multi-Channel Ecommerce Accounting</a><a class="dropdown-item" href="real-time-ecommerce-profit-tracking.html"  >Real-Time Ecommerce Profit Tracking</a><a class="dropdown-item" href="bookkeeping-for-digital-products.html"  >Bookkeeping for Digital Products</a><a class="dropdown-item" href="ecommerce-accounts-payable-management.html"  >Ecommerce Accounts Payable Management</a><a class="dropdown-item" href="sales-channel-integration-for-bookkeeping.html"  >Sales Channel Integration for Bookkeeping</a><a class="dropdown-item" href="inventory-valuation-for-ecommerce.html"  >Inventory Valuation for Ecommerce</a><a class="dropdown-item" href="bookkeeping-for-ecommerce-businesses.html"  >Bookkeeping for Ecommerce Businesses</a><a class="dropdown-item" href="recurring-expense-tracking.html"  >Recurring Expense Tracking</a><a class="dropdown-item" href="vendor-management-for-ecommerce.html"  >Vendor Management for Ecommerce</a><a class="dropdown-item" href="product-returns-bookkeeping.html"  >Product Returns Bookkeeping</a><a class="dropdown-item" href="automatic-transaction-categorization.html"  >Automatic Transaction Categorization</a><a class="dropdown-item" href="ecommerce-expense-tracking-tools.html"  >Ecommerce Expense Tracking Tools</a><a class="dropdown-item" href="cogs-calculation-for-ecommerce.html"  >Cogs Calculation for Ecommerce</a><a class="dropdown-item" href="ecommerce-financial-forecasting.html"  >Ecommerce Financial Forecasting</a><a class="dropdown-item" href="ecommerce-payment-gateway-integration.html"  >Ecommerce Payment Gateway Integration</a><a class="dropdown-item" href="advanced-reporting-for-ecommerce-bookkeeping.html"  >Advanced Reporting for Ecommerce Bookkeeping</a><a class="dropdown-item" href="bookkeeping-for-ecommerce-subscription-services.html"  >Bookkeeping for Ecommerce Subscription Services</a></div>
</li>
<li class="nav-item"><a class="nav-link bccd5f007a9ef819a33b706381fe41441" rel=nofollow href="about-us.html">About Us</a>
</li><li class="nav-item">
<a class="btn btn-md bea14ca84507e18b21dddfb9118578681" href="https://online-accounting.co.uk/contact/" rel="nofollow">Contact Us</a>
</li>
</ul>
</div>
</nav>
<section class="container" style="min-height: 80vh;">
<h1>Privacy Policy for online accounting</h1>
<p>At online accounting one of our main priorities is the privacy of our visitors.
 This Privacy Policy document contains types of information that is collected and recorded by online accounting and how we use it. You can check out our main website here: https://online-accounting.co.uk/</p>
<p>If you have additional questions or require more information about our Privacy Policy, do not hesitate to contact us.</p>
<p>This Privacy Policy only applies to our online activities and is valid for visitors to our website with regards to the information that they shared and/or collect in online accounting. This policy is not applicable to any information collected offline or via channels other than this website. </p>
<h2>Consent</h2>
<p>By using our website, you hereby consent to our Privacy Policy and agree to its terms.</p>
<h2>Information we collect</h2>
<p>The personal information that you are asked to provide, and the reasons why you are asked to provide it, will be made clear to you at the point we ask you to provide your personal information.</p>
<p>If you contact us directly, we may receive additional information about you such as your name, email address, phone number, the contents of the message and/or attachments you may send us, and any other information you may choose to provide.</p>
<p>When you register for an Account, we may ask for your contact information, including items such as name, online accounting, address, email address, and telephone number.</p>
<h2>How we use your information</h2>
<p>We use the information we collect in various ways, including to:</p>
<ul>
<li>Provide, operate, and maintain our website</li>
<li>Improve, personalize, and expand our website</li>
<li>Understand and analyze how you use our website</li>
<li>Develop new products, services, features, and functionality</li>
<li>Communicate with you, either directly or through one of our partners, including for customer service, to provide you with updates and other information relating to the website, and for marketing and promotional purposes</li>
<li>Send you emails</li>
<li>Find and prevent fraud</li>
</ul>
<h2>Log Files</h2>
<p>online accounting follows a standard procedure of using log files. These files log visitors when they visit websites. All hosting companies do this and a part of hosting services' analytics. The information collected by log files include internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, Internet Service Provider (ISP), date and time stamp, referring/exit pages, and possibly the number of clicks. These are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable. The purpose of the information is for analyzing trends, administering the site, tracking users' movement on the website, and gathering demographic information.</p>
<h2>Advertising Partners Privacy Policies</h2>
<P>You may consult this list to find the Privacy Policy for each of the advertising partners of online accounting.</p>
<p>Third-party ad servers or ad networks uses technologies like cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons that are used in their respective advertisements and links that appear on online accounting, which are sent directly to users' browser. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. These technologies are used to measure the effectiveness of their advertising campaigns and/or to personalize the advertising content that you see on websites that you visit.</p>
<p>Note that online accounting has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.</p>
<h2>Third Party Privacy Policies</h2>
<p>online accounting's Privacy Policy does not apply to other advertisers or websites. Thus, we are advising you to consult the respective Privacy Policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information. It may include their practices and instructions about how to opt-out of certain options. </p>
<p>You can choose to disable cookies through your individual browser options. To know more detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers, it can be found at the browsers' respective websites.</p>
<h2>CCPA Privacy Rights (Do Not Sell My Personal Information)</h2>
<p>Under the CCPA, among other rights, California consumers have the right to:</p>
<p>Request that a business that collects a consumer's personal data disclose the categories and specific pieces of personal data that a business has collected about consumers.</p>
<p>Request that a business delete any personal data about the consumer that a business has collected.</p>
<p>Request that a business that sells a consumer's personal data, not sell the consumer's personal data.</p>
<p>If you make a request, we have one month to respond to you. If you would like to exercise any of these rights, please contact us.</p>
<h2>GDPR Data Protection Rights</h2>
<p>We would like to make sure you are fully aware of all of your data protection rights. Every user is entitled to the following:</p>
<p>The right to access – You have the right to request copies of your personal data. We may charge you a small fee for this service.</p>
<p>The right to rectification – You have the right to request that we correct any information you believe is inaccurate. You also have the right to request that we complete the information you believe is incomplete.</p>
<p>The right to erasure – You have the right to request that we erase your personal data, under certain conditions.</p>
<p>The right to restrict processing – You have the right to request that we restrict the processing of your personal data, under certain conditions.</p>
<p>The right to object to processing – You have the right to object to our processing of your personal data, under certain conditions.</p>
<p>The right to data portability – You have the right to request that we transfer the data that we have collected to another organization, or directly to you, under certain conditions.</p>
<p>If you make a request, we have one month to respond to you. If you would like to exercise any of these rights, please contact us.</p>
<h2>Children's Information</h2>
<p>Another part of our priority is adding protection for children while using the internet. We encourage parents and guardians to observe, participate in, and/or monitor and guide their online activity.</p>
<p>online accounting does not knowingly collect any Personal Identifiable Information from children under the age of 13. If you think that your child provided this kind of information on our website, we strongly encourage you to contact us immediately and we will do our best efforts to promptly remove such information from our records.</p>
<h2>Publisher</h2>
<p>
This website is owned and published by:
online accounting</br>
</br>
Head Office More Than Accountants Burnden House Viking Street</br>
Bolton </br>
Lancashire</br>
https://online-accounting.co.uk/</br>
contact@online-accounting.co.uk</br>
</p>
</section>
<footer>
<div class="pt-5 container py-4" >
<div class="row"><div class="col-lg-3">
<p>online accounting</p>
<p>Email : contact@online-accounting.co.uk</p>
<p>City : Bolton </p>
<p>State : Lancashire</p>
<p>Zip : BL 2LL</p>
<p>Address : Head Office More Than Accountants Burnden House Viking Street</p>
<p>Company Website : <a class="bccd5f007a9ef819a33b706381fe41441" href="https://online-accounting.co.uk/" rel="nofollow">https://online-accounting.co.uk/</a></p>
</div><div class="col-lg-3">
<p>USEFUL LINKS</p>
<p><a class="bccd5f007a9ef819a33b706381fe41441" href="https://seoyeconsultancy.blob.core.windows.net/linkmybooks/linkmybooks/index.html"  target="_blank">how to automate Amazon FBA accounting with Link My Books   </a></p><p><a class="bccd5f007a9ef819a33b706381fe41441" href="https://storage.googleapis.com/onlineaccounting/linkmybooks/ecommerce-bookkeeping-solutions.html"  target="_blank">ecommerce bookkeeping</a></p><p><a class="bccd5f007a9ef819a33b706381fe41441" href="https://linkmybooks.b-cdn.net/linkmybooks/index.html"  target="_blank">ecommerce bookkeeping services</a></p><p><a class="bccd5f007a9ef819a33b706381fe41441" href="https://onlineaccounting.s3.eu-central-003.backblazeb2.com/linkmybooks/index.html"  target="_blank">bookkeeping for ecommerce</a></p><p><a class="bccd5f007a9ef819a33b706381fe41441" href="https://objectstorage.ap-melbourne-1.oraclecloud.com/n/axxtfkighssr/b/onlineaccounting/o/linkmybooks/index.html"  target="_blank">Link My Books setup for Amazon FBA accounting beginners</a></p><p><a class="bccd5f007a9ef819a33b706381fe41441" href="https://onlineaccounting.s3.syd.ap.cloud-object-storage.appdomain.cloud/linkmybooks/index.html"  target="_blank">step-by-step Amazon FBA accounting automation with Link My Books</a></p>
<p><a class="bccd5f007a9ef819a33b706381fe41441" href="https://algocentric.neocities.org//onlineaccounting/linkmybooks/index.html"  target="_blank">easy Amazon FBA accounting setup using Link My Books</a></p>
</div><div class="col-lg-3"><p><a class="bccd5f007a9ef819a33b706381fe41441" href="sitemap.html" rel="nofollow">Sitemap</a></p>
<p><a class="bccd5f007a9ef819a33b706381fe41441" href="privacy-policy.html" rel="nofollow">Privacy Policy</a></p>
<p><a class="bccd5f007a9ef819a33b706381fe41441" href="about-us.html" rel="nofollow">About Us</a></p>
</p>
</div></div>
</div>
</footer> 
<script type="text/javascript">
document.addEventListener('DOMContentLoaded', function() {
var dropdowns = document.querySelectorAll('.dropdown-hover');
function showDropdown() {
var dropdownMenu = this.querySelector('.dropdown-menu');
dropdownMenu.style.display = 'block';
}
function hideDropdown() {
var dropdownMenu = this.querySelector('.dropdown-menu');
dropdownMenu.style.display = 'none';
}
function handleClick(event) {
var target = event.target;
window.location.href = target.getAttribute('href');
}
dropdowns.forEach(function(dropdown) {
dropdown.addEventListener('mouseenter', showDropdown);
dropdown.addEventListener('mouseleave', hideDropdown);
var dropdownMenu = dropdown.querySelector('.dropdown-toggle');
dropdownMenu.addEventListener('click', handleClick);
});
});
</script> 
</body>
</html>
